<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Marco Rios Site</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Marco Rios</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 15:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>El Senado Español rechaza revisar a la baja el IVA cultural</title>
		<link>/espanol-el-senado-rechaza-revisar-a-la-baja-el-iva-cultural/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aronmusic.com/?p=1553</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[El pleno del Senado ha rechazado con los votos del PP (84 a favor y 146 en contra) una moción consecuencia de interpelación presentada por CiU, que buscaba revisar el tipo impositivo del IVA a las prestaciones de servicios culturales con el fin de aplicar el IVA reducido al sector cultural, tal y como ocurre en la mayoría de los países de la Unión Europea.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>La Ley de Darwin &#8211; Gira 2013</title>
		<link>/la-ley-de-darwin-gira-2013/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 16:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aronmusic.com/?p=1571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tres profesores entran en una biblioteca. No van cargados con libros. No visten chaquetas a cuadros ni caminan encogiendo los hombros. No llevan tiza en las manos, gafas redondas ni maletín. Arrastran un amplificador Fender Twin Reverb Blackface del 66 que han pasado por debajo del mostrador ante la mirada despistada de la vieja encargada. En una mano una funda de guitarra. En la otra una carpeta tatuada de fórmulas, exámenes por corregir y un buen puñado de canciones escritas a mano. Saludan a los presentes ante la mirada atónita de quienes se cruzan en su camino. Las mesas están inundadas de estudiantes que bucean entre miles de páginas y apuntes, ausentes del planeta Tierra, en calma, sumidos en un profundo misterio. Los profesores llegan a su objetivo, justo en el centro de la sala. Lanzan un cable. Sacan los instrumentos. Se suben a la mesa. Se ruega silencio, por favor. Las fechas confirmadas hasta el momento son: 26 de Abril &#8211; Fuente de Cantos (Festival ChanfaRock) 10 de Mayo &#8211; Sala Lousiana &#8211; Sevilla 11 de Mayo &#8211; Sala Habana &#8211; Huelva 31 de Mayo &#8211; Sala Babylonia &#8211; Cádiz 15 de Junio &#8211; Fórum Plaza &#8211; Granada 21 de Junio &#8211; Sala Góngora &#8211; Córdoba 22 de Junio &#8211; La Cochera &#8211; Málaga Puedes comprar tus entradas a&#160;través&#160;del sistema Ticketa (www.ticketea.com). Mas info en la web oficial de la banda (www.laleydedarwin.com) o en 2Giras Management (www.2giras.com) Permanezcan atentos, saquen sus cuadernos y tomen nota… porque presentamos el primer Videoclip de La Ley de Darwin y su canción Buscando una salida. Grabado en múltiples localizaciones, este vídeo presenta a este grupo de profesores al borde de la locura, huyendo de su rutina. Una combinación peligrosa entre ciencia y música, y un primer single salvaje, cargado de fuerza que ya [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aron Music signs a pioneering contract worldwide entertainment</title>
		<link>/espanol-aron-music-firma-contrato-pionero-en-entretenimiento-mundial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 01:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aronmusic.com/?p=1479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[El 18 de septiembre pasado, Aron Music International, empresa multinacional dedicada a la producción de eventos y conciertos, recientemente firmó un contrato de exclusividad con la firma Coreana &#8220;Korean HD Broadcasting Corporation&#8221;, empresa más grande de Asia de contenidos HD y 3D, dueños de diversos canales de televisión por paga, con el fin de realizar la grabación y distribución de las producciones en formatos de 2D, 3D y Full HD en todos los shows realizados en América, Asia y Europa. Marco Ríos, C.E.O. y fundador de Aron Music, manifestó que “este trato abre nuevas oportunidades para nuestra empresa, de este modo podremos acceder a un modelo de trabajo diferente”, con esto Aron Music International se ubica como empresa pionera dentro de este campo. Países como Chile, Perú, Paraguay, Argentina, España, Portugal, Emiratos Arabes, Tailandia, China, Taiwan y Japón, donde Aron ha empezado operaciones de manera formal, se verán beneficiados con contenidos exclusivos de la mejor calidad en materia de shows y conciertos.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hong Kong Ballet &#8211; Moments in Time, Live in HK</title>
		<link>/the-hong-kong-ballet-asian-tour/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 01:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aronmusic.com/?p=1111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Hong Kong Ballet presents an evening of ballets created exclusively for us. The Company has sought out three of today’s most promising contemporary choreographers, Peter Quanz, Kinsun Chan and Fei Bo, and brought them to Hong Kong. We commissioned them to create new ballets for our dancers, with our dancers; this collaborative creative process has generated three ballets that showcase the Company as a whole, as well as celebrating the unique physique, talent and personality of each dancer. With this trio of powerful, stimulating and thought-provoking works, The Hong Kong Ballet proudly supports the choreographers of the future. LUMINOUS Is a happy, ever-lasting relationship really possible between a man and a woman? Peter Quanz speaks through his choreography about the fragility of human relationships, the tension between the genders and the qualities drawn out of us by each passing alliance. This emotionally-charged piece, dripping with sensuality, will make you reflect on your own relationships past and present. Choreography: Peter Quanz Music: Affairs of the Heart by Marjan Mozetich Costume Designer : Anne Armit Lighting Design: Mak Kwok Fai Re-lighting: Goh Boon Ann ***** BLACK ON BLACK Kinsun Chan&#8217;s new ballet explores the timelessness of the colour black, and the dance aesthetics he has created reflect the many facets of black&#8217;s symbolism. Kinsun manipulates the space on stage, playing with contrasting movements to reflect the contradictory emotions aroused by the colour black. The choreographer incorporates his intrigue for body language and gestures into this ballet of power, passion and surprise. Choreography: Kinsun Chan Music: String Quartet No. 2, Op. 64 “Quasi Una Fantasia” by Henryk Górecki Set and Costume Design: Kinsun Chan Lighting Design: Goh Boon Ann ***** A ROOM OF HER OWN Frustration, self-doubt, jealousy and torment; these are just a few of the emotions felt by Lu Xi, [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Festival Orchestra 2011/2012</title>
		<link>/hong-kong-festival-orchestra-2011/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 02:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aronmusic.com/?p=1130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2011 Summer Concert The Hong Kong Festival Orchestra is now accepting applications for the 2011 season. This year we are proud to have Mr. Leung Kin Fung, First Associate Concertmaster of the Hong Kong Philharmonic Orchestra, as well as emerging stars violist Born Lau to be our guest soloists for the 2011 summer concerts. Concert dates: August 22, 23 , 2011 Tentative Rehearsals: August 1 to August 22, every Monday, Wednesday and Friday evening. Application Fee: $ (Free of charge) Participation Fee: $ (Free of charge) Concert Repertoire: •Tchaikovsky Violin Concerto In D, Op. 35 (Soloist: Leung Kin Fung) •Bruch Romance for Viola &#38; Orchestra, Op. 85 (Soloist: Born Lau) •Smetana The Moldau from Ma Vlast •Bizet &#8220;Carmen&#8221; Suite, Prelude I, Allegro giocoso •Sibelius Symphony No. 2, Op. 43 Applicants must submit the following to directors@hkfo.org as attachments: 1.The application form in PDF format. The form can be downloaded from http://www.hkfo.org/application.pdf 2.A recording of the listed audition excerpts for the applicant&#8217;s respective instrument If the file sizes of audio recordings are too big to be sent as attachments, you may send the audio files in compressed .zip formats or through transferbigfiles.com with audio files named according to the following format: &#8220;ChrisWongViola.mp3&#8221; i.e. (Your name + your instrument).mp3 Note: Recordings need not be in professional or studio quality, but the sound quality should be as good as possible so as to not detract from the soloist&#8217;s capabilities. Audition Requirements •Strings: Mendelssohn Midsummer Night&#8217;s Dream &#8211; first page of the scherzo •Flutes: Mendelssohn Midsummer Night&#8217;s Dream &#8211; scherzo (solo at the end) •Oboes: Ravel Le Tombeau de Couperin &#8211; I. Prelude (beginning to rehearsal 2) •Clarinets: Mendelssohn Midsummer Night&#8217;s Dream &#8211; first page of the scherzo •Bassoons: Mozart The Marriage of Figaro &#8211; Overture &#8211; m. 139-171 •Horns: Brahms Variations on a [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
