<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Publications &#8211; Marco Rios Site</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/publications/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Marco Rios</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 09:54:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hosting Events as a Tool for Restoring Destination Image</title>
		<link>/hosting-events-tool-restoring-destination-image/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Rios]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Publications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2220</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Restoration of destination image has become a necessity in the global world when negative perception can be a barrier in attracting tourism. One strategy applied by destination marketers to improve the image of places experiencing an immediate or prolonged crisis is hosting spotlight events. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Attributional Model of Visitors’ Event Experience in Festivals and  Special Events</title>
		<link>/attributional-model-visitors-event-experience-festivals-special-events/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Rios]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 12:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Publications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Attribution theory is a constructive and effective application in understanding the behavioural psychology of consumers. Psychologically, individuals normally make some kind of inference from their personal analysis of behavioural facts and figures encountered on-site in order to explain an event or outcome. Subsequently, causal inferences influence individuals’ actions regardless of accuracy, quick form or biased attributions. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goals and Objectives of Event Management Associations</title>
		<link>/goals-objectives-event-management-associations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Rios]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 10:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Publications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2019</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the event management industry grows and consolidates worldwide, associations play an increasingly significant role in professional support to the industry by ensuring the continued growth and success of event management professionals.  Although there are many events, which are successfully crewed by volunteers, the increasing competition to secure major events is giving some impetus to the trend to create fully professionalised events. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Music Festival Motivators for Attendance: Developing an Agenda for Research</title>
		<link>/music-festival-motivators-attendance-developing-agenda-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Rios]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Publications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This paper analyses existing research with reference to motivations for attending special events with specific reference to musical performances. Its purpose is to identify emerging themes, detect similarities and contradictions, and uncover gaps in knowledge that need to be addressed by further research.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raising Environmental Responsibility And Sustainability For Sport Events: A Systematic Review</title>
		<link>/raising-environmental-responsibility-sustainability-sport-events-systematic-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Rios]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 12:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Publications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sport events and associated venues impose a significant impact on the environment. Athletes, coaches, officials, athletes’ entourage, and spectators travel to sport competitions using planes, trains, buses and cars. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>La industria de la música se reinventa</title>
		<link>/la-industria-de-la-musica-se-reinventa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Publications]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aronmusic.com/?p=942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Entre finales de los 60 y mediados de los 70, la industria de la música estaba lejos del declive económico. Eran los años en que Eric Clapton veía cómo los Rolling Stones pagaban a gente sólo para vaciar ceniceros y David Bowie o Kiss emprendían mastodónticas giras llenas de efectos, con discos detrás que los respaldaban y que vendían decenas de millones de copias. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
